Modern love is a dangerous game.
The Tinder Swindler is a documentary, crime film directed by Felicity Morris.
Posing as a wealthy, jet-setting diamond mogul, an Israeli conman wooed
women online then conned them out of millions of dollars.
Now, some victims plan for payback.
Self (archive footage), played by Shimon Yehuda Hayut.
Self, played by Cecilie Fjellhøy.
Self, played by Pernilla Sjöholm.
Self, played by Ayleen Charlotte.
Self, played by Kristoffer Kumar.
Self, played by Erlend Ofte Arntsen.
The Tinder Swindler is a British true crime documentary film directed by Felicity
Morris and released to streaming on Netflix on 2 February 2022.
The documentary tells the story of the Israeli conman Simon Leviev (born Shimon Hayut) who used the dating application Tinder to connect with individuals who
he then emotionally manipulated into financially supporting his lavish lifestyle on the pretext he needed the money to escape his "enemies".
The film explores themes of con man, fraud,
dating, con, meeting on the internet.